The first subtitle
This is crazy. Second subtitle
Third one
Here is the fourth subtile, it will
be autofitted to the given
point in the parameters
We can talk, sir.
- Oh, I see. So it's personal?
- No, you intimidate them.
Good God, These are subtitles which
works directly with the videos.
I mean, this is the same format as any other subtitles.
- I thought of you as a soldier first.
- I'm an airman.
You have, actually,
excellent bone structure, there.
I'm kind of having a hard time
not looking at you now.
Is that weird? Come on, it's okay, laugh.
- Sir, I have a question to ask.
- Yes, please.
Is it true you went 12 for 12
with last year's Maxim cover models?
That is an excellent question.
Yes and no.
March and I had a scheduling conflict,
but fortunately,
the Christmas cover was twins.
Anything else? You're kidding me
with the hand up, right?
- Is it cool if I take a picture with you?
- Yes. It's very cool.
All right.
I don't want to see this
on your MySpace page.
Please, no gang signs.
No, throw it up. I'm kidding.
Yeah, peace. I love peace.
I'd be out of a job with peace.
Come on. Hurry up. Just click it.
Don't change any settings. Just click it.
- What's going on?
- Contact left!
What have we got?
Jimmy, stay with Stark!
- Stay down!
- Yeah.
Son of a bitch!
- Wait, wait, wait! Give me a gun!
- Stay here!
Whoa!
Tony Stark.
Visionary. Genius.
American patriot.
Even from an early age,
the son of legendary
weapons developer Howard Stark
quickly stole the spotlight
with his brilliant and unique mind.
At age four,
he built his first circuit board.
At age six, his first engine.
And at 17, he graduated
summa cum laude from MIT.
Then, the passing of a titan.
Howard Stark's lifelong friend
and ally, Obadiah Stane,
steps in to help fill the gap
left by the legendary founder,
until, at age 21, the prodigal son returns
and is anointed the new CEO
of Stark industries.
With the keys to the kingdom,
Tony ushers in a new era
for his father's legacy,
creating smarter weapons,
advanced robotics, satellite targeting.
Today, Tony Stark has changed
the face of the weapons industry
by ensuring freedom
and protecting America
and her interests around the globe.
As liaison to Stark Industries,
I've had the unique privilege
of serving with a real patriot.
He is my friend
and he is my great mentor.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is my honor
to present this year's Apogee Award
to Mr. Tony Stark.
Tony?
- Thank you, Colonel.
- Thanks for the save.
This is beautiful. Thank you.
Thank you all very much.
This is wonderful.
Well, I'm not Tony Stark.
But if I were Tony,
I would tell you how honored I feel
and what a joy it is
to receive this very prestigious award.
Tony, you know...
The best thing about Tony
is also the worst thing.
He's always working.
Work it! Come on!
- We should just stay till the morning.
- You are unbelievable.
- Oh, no! Did they rope you into this?
- Nobody roped me into anything!
- I'm so sorry.
- But they told me that
if I presented you with an award,
you'd be deeply honored.
Of course I'd be deeply honored.
And it's you, that's great.
- So when do we do it?
- It's right here.
- Here you go.
- There it is. That was easy.
- I'm so sorry.
- Yeah, it's okay.
Wow! Would you look at that?
That's something else.
I don't have any of those
floating around.
We're gonna let it ride!
Give me a hand, will you?
Give me a little something-something.
Okay, you, too.
- I don't blow on a man's dice.
- Come on, honey bear.
There it is.
Lieutenant Colonel Rhodes rolls! And...
Two craps. Line away.
- That's what happens.
- Worse things have happened.
I think we're gonna be fine.
Color me up, will you?
- This is where I exit.
- All right.
Tomorrow, don't be late.
- Yeah, you can count on it.
- I'm serious!
I know, I know.
Render unto Caesar
that which is Caesar's. There you go.
Mr. Stark! Excuse me, Mr. Stark!
Christine Everhart,
Vanity Fair magazine.